Okay, now that we now know how to chain
um promises and thens together to do
multiple operations that depend upon
each other, it's time to go back and
look at our callback code. So, if we
remember this terrible monstrosity, it's
time to simplify it a little bit. I'm
going to leave it here so you can see
it, but I'm going to comment it out and
I'm going to paste in the equivalent
when you're using promises.
So what we did is we said wait once
you've waited take the return value of
wait and because the return value is a
promise um we want you to wait until it
resolves and then log out the result and
then wait again then log the result then
wait again then log the result and it's
going to keep doing this. But if you
look at this, this code is so much
easier to read because you know it's
going to run this then, then it's going
to run this then, then then it's going
to run this then in order. And so
instead of having to figure out this
whole tree structure of callback
functions, you can take advantage of
promises to write then multiple times.
And I know now it's going to wait 5
seconds, then three, sorry, 3 seconds,
then five, then two, then four, then
one, then five, and it's just going to
keep going down that list. And I know
that it works that way because these
dotns are all chained together neatly.
And now I don't have this giant nested
structure that was going to keep nesting
further and further to the right until
it was off the screen. And so promises
are a way to simplify the way you write
your code. And it helps you avoid having
to write this many callback functions.
Um but and if this still looks like a
pain to you, that's cuz it still can't
be. And I am going to show you another
way to do this in the next video. So
we'll have a little moment of silence
for these developers, but way less short
of a moment of silence than we had for
the developers who had to write
callbacks. That's just terrible. Um, so
in the next video I'll show you another
fun way that makes it cuz it would be
nice if rather than writing our
asynchronous code like this is if we
wrote our asynchronous code like we
write our synchronous code. Wouldn't it
be nice if our JavaScript looked exactly
the same for functions that needed to
run in the background as it did for
functions that run normally? And if you
are thinking that great because there is
a way to do